ICICI Lomb has launched a new plan
called Elevate. This plan has
five things that are
not
available in any of the existing health insurance companies. What is there in this plan that
other companies are not offering? We will
find out. So watch the video till the end. If you are
new to the channel, then subscribe to the channel and do not
forget to press the bell icon
so that in the future you can get all the insurance and
finance related information
that customers are looking for today. So
let's start the video directly here. So
guys, I was talking
about ICICI Lomb's Elevate plan. So, guys, in
this plan, first of all, you get an increasing
claim amount and an increasing bonus. These are the
benefits which have completely changed this plan
and have completely changed the entire health insurance
industry. So, do
not forget to watch the video till the end. So, first
we will talk about the basic benefits which are
in the policy. Before the benefits, we will
talk about what is eligible, what is the sum
in shares and what are the conditions.  Are there waiting
periods, are there advances, are there five
best advances that I have told you that
you are going to get in this policy, the
entry age in this policy is 18 and the
maximum entry age is 125 years,
secondly let's talk about sum in short,
how much is your coverage in this, you have coverage of 5 lakhs, 75 lakhs,
10 lakhs, 15 lakhs, 20 lakhs, 25 lakhs,
50 lakhs, 1 crore, 3 crores and there is
also unlimited coverage, you can take this policy for one
year, two years, three years,
you get additional discount on taking it for two years and three years,
definitely take that plus if you
want a policy, then you
can have husband, wife and three others together in a family floater policy,
so you
can take a policy for a maximum of five members, the
child in one policy will be considered till the age of 30,
age of one child in the same policy, now let's talk about
basic benefits,
day care surgery is all covered in the policy, no
list has been provided, meaning that some such
surgeries  It is in which you do
not need to be admitted in the hospital, you
go for five to seven hours for the whole day and
get treatment and come back, then that surgery
is also covered under the policy, plus
your pre and post hospitalization, that is,
expenses for 90 days before admission and expenses for 180 days after discharge,
you
can also get the money back and if we
talk about organ donor, then
your organ donor is covered up to the sum in shot under the policy, that is,
if you are donating your organ to
someone like kidney etc.,
you are donating any body part to
someone, then its amount will be
covered up to the sum in shot, up to the sum in shot
means whatever coverage you have given, 10 lakh, 20 lakh,
30 lakh, 50 lakh, whatever the next benefit is, treatment, home
treatment, that is, if
you want treatment at home, then you can get the treatment done at home as well,
three days
treatment is necessary, then you
can cover that expense also, for treatment at home
either hospital or hospital  If bed
is not available or the doctor has advised
that your condition is critical, then you
can take treatment at home. There is another condition which is
called if there is curfew or such a
condition outside, then in that condition also you
can take treatment at home. If we talk about road ambulance, then
that too
is covered up to summary shots in the policy. Ayurvedic, Nani
Siddha, Homeopathic treatment etc., all of that is
also covered up to summary shots in the policy.
You also have a reset benefit in this policy.
It is called reset benefit. For example, if
you took a policy of Rs. 10 lakhs, Rs. 10
lakhs got exhausted, a claim came again, you will
get Rs. 10 lakhs again. If a claim
comes again, then you will get Rs. 10 lakhs again. What I
mean to say is that whatever coverage you are taking,
you can take that coverage as many times as you want
and the extra coverage you
get, you can use it for any disease. There is no
condition. Let us
talk about bonus which is called no claim bonus.
Your no claim is included in the policy.  There is also a claim bonus of
20, 20, 20, 20, 20. You will get bonus five times.
By doing 20, 20, your policy of 10 will
increase from 20, 20. I have
taken the example of 10 lakhs, so I am telling you in terms of 10 lakhs, that
means your policy of 10
lakhs will become of 12 lakhs, then 14 lakhs, then 16 lakhs, then
18 lakhs, then 20 lakhs. If you do
not make claims continuously for five years, then
this is your next benefit, your wellness
benefit. What you get in this is that you
get a discount of up to 30% on renewal. Next
year, if you want, you can reduce your premium.
Next year, you have to
download an app of IIC,
you can download that app and what you do with it is that you
can collect some points.
How to collect those points? To collect those points,
you have to follow the steps per day. If you follow
those steps, then the
points you have will keep getting on it. If you
want, you can also download Naval's app.  You
can avail a discount of up to 30% on time. Another important
thing is bariatric surgery.
What does bariatric surgery mean?
Obesity surgery is
not covered by many insurance companies,
but under this plan, that too
is covered up to sum of Rs. If we talk about
modern treatment,
what does modern treatment mean? Earlier,
it was not covered under insurance;
if it was, then it was covered by very limited companies
or it was available up to Rs. 1 lakh.
Modern treatment is that
where you are going to make a claim and
the treatment in which you are being
treated robotically, like chemotherapy
etc., okay, in that condition, what is it that
today's time, technology has become so high, there were
very few companies in India which used to cover such operations
according to robotics, which is called modern treatment according to technology,
okay, so that
type of treatment is also
covered under the policy today. The most important
thing is that it is covered up to sum of Rs. 1 lakh, which no
other company is offering.  Except two,
you can also take maternity coverage under this plan,
that too is covered under your policy.
Now let's talk about waiting periods.
In dental policy, it is linked to the same day on which
you took the policy. If you want to claim for normal and critical
illness, then you
can claim after 30 days. If you want to
claim for surgery, then
all surgeries are covered only after 30 days, but there are
some surgeries which are covered after 2 years
like cataract, stone,
hernia, slipped sinus, uterus, fibroid,
ENT. In this way, in every company, there are 14 to
15 or maximum 1718 surgeries
which are covered under the insurance after 2 years.
If you already have any
problem, then you will get a claim for that
after 3 years.
Your premium will be calculated under this policy, which will be
calculated according to the zone. The company has
kept four types of zones in the policy, zone
A, B, C, D, meaning is like this  Let's
talk about the cities of Zone A, Mumbai,
Ghaziabad, I am talking about big cities,
Delhi, okay,
big cities like that, let's
talk about Zone A, Zone B, like Pune, Kolkata,
Bangalore, in this way let's talk about Zone C,
like Chhattisgarh,
Himachal Pradesh, Jammu and Kashmir, in
this way the cities of your Zone 3 will
come under Zone D, now let's talk about Zone D, all the
remaining cities, even the smallest ones, all of them will
come under Zone D,
but the most important thing is
that under this policy you will
not be charged zone wise copayment, it means that if you are
in Zone D, that is,
you live in the smallest city and you are going for treatment,
in Zone A, that is,
you are going for treatment in a big city, then you
can get the treatment done, it is not that you will
get the claim on 80% or 90%, you will get the full claim
100%. Now let's talk about
how you can save money on renewal,
as I told you about the wellness option
which  This is your wellness benefit, in which
you get a discount of up to 30%. You have to follow
some steps on renewal, based on
that. The second is yours, if you
renew the policy
30 days before the next year's fair, then
you will be given an additional discount of 2.5%. The
third option is yours, if you
want the policy, then you can take it for 2 years or 3 years.
You get a discount of 10% on 2 years and up to 15% on 3 years.
You can add many advances or riders in this policy. What
are the riders? First of all, yours is critical
illness. Under this policy, 20
critical illnesses are covered. The maximum
coverage is available up to 50 lakhs. And
you
can take this cover only for customers up to the age of 50 years. Plus, a
personal accident
add-on is also available in this policy. This add-on is for coverage up to 50 lakhs.  It
is available and customers up to 65 years of age
can take it. The next add-on is
your voluntary co-payment. What it means is that
if you want, you
can reduce your premium. If you have taken a policy of Rs. 10 lakh and
feel that the premium is coming high, then
take a co-payment of Rs. 10. What it means is that
whatever claim comes, the company will give you the claim on Rs. 90.
You have to pay from your pocket. The
options that you will get in this are Rs. 10, Rs.
20, Rs. 30, Rs. 40, Rs. 50.
Your maternity coverage is available under this policy
but
I forgot to tell you about the waiting period for maternity. As I will
tell you, the waiting
period for maternity is two years. If you
want, you can reduce it to one year. The
name of the rider is Option to Reduce
Maternity Waiting Period.
Your consultation is also available under this policy. If you want, you can
download the app and listen to
your video audio through it.  You
can do teleconsultation, if you have any
problem then you can discuss
with the company doctor, that option
is also available in the policy and you
can do this unlimited times, there are many other
addons which you can include in the policy,
but the addon which I am going to talk about now, there are
five such addons which are the
best, due to which this plan has become so
famous, so the first addon is
your inflate bonus, for example, you took a policy of 10 lakhs, if a claim comes, you will get 1 crore, but this will be available only once in the entire life, the third addon is your inflate
bonus, in this policy if you want, you
can give as much bonus as you want, there is
no limit, the coverage will keep increasing, but this
Kamle Vi bonus
comes in the name of power booster, so  You
can include this in your policy.
After this is your infighting.
What this means is that there are
five such diseases in the policy which you
can claim after 90 days under the policy. It
comes in the name of Jump Start Rider.
BP, Diabetes, Asthma, Cholesterol. There is another
disease, to know its name,
comment in the comment box. Illness. After this, the last
term is your infighting.
Then you will get 10 lakhs. Once it is over, you will
get 10 lakhs. You can take as much as you want, but
you can take 10 lakhs from the company. So,
these were five such advances which are the
best and are different from all others.
In the line of health insurance, if you are going to take health insurance for your
family or for yourself, then
definitely think about this plan. It is a very good
plan. The premium is also not so high
that you feel that adding all these things will
increase the premium a lot. It is not like that,
many people will find this premium affordable. So
this was the
Elevate plan of ICICI Ltd under health insurance. If
you have any doubt about any
condition regarding this plan,  If you want to know about any waiting period, any
benefits, any add-ons, then
you can call us,
your number is available in the description and
if you want to purchase any health insurance policy or
any life insurance policy or any kind of
insurance, then
you can call us,
your number is available in the description,
so now we will end the video here,
whoever has not subscribed to my channel, please
subscribe to the channel, we will meet like this
in the next video, mind
take care bye bye good bye and bye bye
[Music]